I am building a liminal space, which sounds crazy, but it's happening, and this is something that I wanted to do for
years now.
Really since I came to know liminal spaces back in 2019-2020.
If you don't know what a liminal space is, I'll put some pictures up here, and maybe it will ring some bells.
As you may already know, most of these images are not real.
They're generated in a 3D software, apart from a few of them, which I've been lucky enough to visit one of them.
One of the most popular liminal spaces, the Liminal Space Hotel.
You know, even when I first developed my fascination for liminal spaces, I couldn't shake the desire to just want to be there.
Like, actually be there.
Because what they made me feel, the feeling they invoked within me, even just through the screen, was of such clarity and internal
alignment and stillness that I had never experienced before.
And at the time, it always felt like such a distant dream.
But since then, I've come to the realization that I just do my best in general when I throw myself into something.
But why does this affect you?
Well, if you already are familiar with liminal spaces, or maybe you even have a bit of a fascination for them yourself, then you probably
have already felt the kind of feelings that they invoke within you.
And if you haven't, then I urge you to simply go on YouTube and type in liminal space playlist or playlist for exploring liminal
spaces, and just read the comments.
People write paragraphs in the comments describing what they feel and the kind of mental state that liminal spaces in general bring them
to.
So this isn't really just a matter of an internet aesthetic.
This isn't simply cool pictures online.
This is something that transcends that.
And it's affecting people and moving people and helping people in a very, very deep way internally.
But until this point, all of this has been done just simply through the screen.
And my goal is to bring this experience into real life,
something that tangible that somebody can immerse themselves within for an extended period of time and experience a complete
internal transformation.
Because the world that we live in today is filled with noise, it's filled with distraction and chaos, and it's really not
healthy for the mind, the body, or the spirit.
But given the nature of the world, it's really hard to kind of get away from those things, given that we kind of have to function within
society, and that's the way it's been built up.
So it's really no one's fault, but it's just the way it is.
The liminal space that I'm creating will be specifically designed to allow somebody to remove themselves from this type of environment, one of distraction and
chaos, with the intention of allowing the individual to reach a place of internal clarity and alignment that will allow them to really
see and understand who and what they are to a very deep degree that will transform their life.
Now, what this results in for the average individual that exists within this type of environment is a real lack of sense of self, a lack of
identity.
And when you don't really understand your true nature, you know, who and what you really are, then you really lose a sense of how to orient
yourself in the world, what you truly align with, the right and wrong decisions to make, as well as a lack of direction and
clarity in the present time and also in the future.
And this just leaves people feeling depressed, anxious, and really just that their everyday life lacks
meaning and purpose.
So, if we want to understand our identity to a deeper degree, and our identity is found within, then we need to remove the
distractions.
We need to remove the noise and allow the dust to settle so that we can see what is real and what is pure.
I mean, just think about it.
You know, you wake up, you probably go on social media the first thing in the morning.
Maybe you have work or you have school for eight hours.
And maybe you go to the gym afterwards, and you're listening to music the Whole time.
And, you know, you go out and you hang out with friends and you socialize.
And you also sleep for eight hours.
So you're just not conscious for eight of those hours.
Maybe you play video games or watch TV.
It's really rare that we ever just kind of with ourselves in silence and without distraction.
And so if our identity is something that's found within, and all of our waking hours are spent invested in things that are external, outside of
us, then how can we understand who and what we really are?
I mean, it only makes sense, you know what I mean?
So at its core, the main use case for the liminal space is to allow the individual to isolate and immerse themselves within an environment
that is removed from distraction and is specifically designed to allow the internal state to start working as it's designed
to, to start putting things into alignment and removing what is not pure, what is not really of you.
And these types of things would be like insecurities, doubts, fears, limiting beliefs, and, you know, skewed perspectives on yourself,
and the way you perceive your life.
All the things that hold us back as individuals, because they aren't of you.
You know, it's not those things aren't really your true nature.
These are kind of things that have found their way into your subconscious and have themselves there through past experiences and judgments of others and from the world
as well, from culture and trends and society in general, are always throughout time as we exist within society
being programmed to some degree subconsciously.
This is mainly where those things come from.
So you could think of it like a detox from those things in a way, allowing you to immerse and empower your identity, the real one.
I actually just got back from a month-long trip to Asia where I spoke about liminality with some of my followers, which was an amazing experience for me.
I can't even put it into words what it feels like to experience seeing this grow its legs.
Whatever you want to call it, a concept, an ideology, a philosophy, I don't even know, just, just, you
know, I've actually learned to not put a label on it or try and, you know, describe it accurately or have the expectation
that I will accurately describe liminality and what it feels like in words because it's just not in
its nature.
I truly believe that the realist, the most profound, the most significant, the truest things in life are better
felt than said.
And seeing it begin to change people's lives all around the world, the same way it has for me.
I mean, liminality is the very reason I'm here today talking to you, is the very reason that I've accomplished some of my lifelong
goals, like achieving 100,000 followers or subscribers on YouTube, which now we're at over 300,000, which is amazing.
My personal brand in general has reached over a million and a half followers across all platforms, and I'm able to travel around the world and host events
and speak to you guys face-to-face about these ideas and about these concepts.
It's just a blessing.
It really is.
I have no other words for it.
But these are the early stages.
I really just entered this new chapter.
So all of the progress that I make in bringing this vision of mine to fruition will be shown in these videos.
The ideation, the concepts, speaking to thought leaders and experts in specific fields that are related to
this, traveling around the world and actually speaking with you guys face to face, diving deeper into this concept and this idea and this
vision, you know, just getting more eyes on it, getting more people talking about it.
Because, man, I just, I just know that this is going to leave a massive impact on the world.
I just, I just do.
I guess you can call it an intuition, but I've dedicated and I am dedicating my life to it.
So you can bet I believe that with 100% certainty.
But I want to hear your guys' ideas, your experience with liminality, with liminal spaces more specifically as well.
How has it moved you?
How has it Changed you?
How has it helped you?
What do you think of them?
You know, just I want to hear more about it from you guys.
So you can bet that I will be reading through all of your comments about liminality.
Nonetheless, I appreciate your time, and I will see you soon.